pinoyechannel.com 2014-06-26

# Privacy Policy - Pinoy e-Channel | Pinoy e-Channel

At pinoyechannel.net, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by pinoyechannel.net and how it is used.

When  registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address or Contact Info. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience – your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.
  * To improve customer service  - your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.
  * To process transactions - Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * To send periodic emails - The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, pinoyechannel.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

Pinoyechannel.net does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on pinoyechannel.net.

.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to pinoyechannel.net and other sites on the Internet.

.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Pinoyechannel.net uses third-party advertising companies in order to provide and support through serving and displaying advertisements. The third-party companies may use cookies and web beacons when you visit pinoyechannel.net which will send the advertisers some information which will include you Internet Protocol (IP) address, Internet Service Provider (ISP), browser you used when visiting pinoyechanel.net, your page views and other relevant information in order to provide advertiser about services of interest wanted by the guest.

Pineyechannel.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Pinoyechannel.net ‘s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.pinoyechannel.net/terms/) section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at pinoyechannel@gmail.com.
